<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Examples on Automated API and Unit testing Docs for OpenFOAM libs</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/categories/examples/</link><description>Recent content in Examples on Automated API and Unit testing Docs for OpenFOAM libs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/categories/examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Example Page</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/example-page/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/example-page/</guid><description>This is a placeholder page. Replace it with your own content.
Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
There should be whitespace between paragraphs. Vape migas chillwave sriracha poutine try-hard distillery. Tattooed shabby chic small batch, pabst art party heirloom letterpress air plant pop-up. Sustainable chia skateboard art party banjo cardigan normcore affogato vexillologist quinoa meggings man bun master cleanse shoreditch readymade.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>Prerequisites Standardese, which we commend you compile from source. An Extended Hugo version (newer than v 0.110.0) Bear for generating compilation database while compiling the code. Whatever the requirements file specifies foamUT if you want to include docs for unit tests. You may take a look at the Apptainer definition file for a quick inspiration on how to install everything that is needed.
Get a copy of the ODW repository You can either use the original ODW as a Template repository, or just fork it the usual way.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/</guid><description>Check the Overview page before anything else. Then you may proceed to installing the dependencies and getting your site up and running.</description></item><item><title>API docs generation</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/api-docs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/api-docs/</guid><description>API documentation (somewhat) relies on in-comments documentation written by the developer, but standardese seems to check it against the actual function signature to make sure the comments don&amp;rsquo;t get outdated. We think that this is still a nice compromise.
Here is a typical workflow to generate API documentation for a repository that manages both the code and documentation website:
Note that it&amp;rsquo;s not recommended to merge the actual code with the docs website.</description></item><item><title>Unit-tests docs generation</title><link>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/ut-docs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://foamscience.github.io/OpenFOAMDocsWebpages/docs/getting-started/ut-docs/</guid><description>All the heavy-lifting is actually done bu foamUT itself, so if you have some unit tests under tests/ folder, they will run and the output is converted over to the webpages under /tests URL. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that your tests must compile as we cannot generate reports on tests that do not compile.
Here is a typical workflow to generate documentation for a repository with some Unit tests:
# Clone the repo which has the code (src/ and test/ folder, where your OpenFOAM libs should reside) git clone https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>